{
  "id": "0",
  "question": "Choose your destiny",
  "answer": "",
  "children": [
    {
      "id": "1",
      "question": "How did they come to New York?",
      "answer": "Novice",
      "children": [
        {
          "id": "1_1",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "Run",
          "children": []
        },
        {
          "id": "1_2",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "Give Up",
          "children": []
        },
        {
          "id": "1_3",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "Die",
          "children": []
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "2",
      "question": "How did they come to London",
      "answer": "Warrior",
      "children": [
        {
          "id": "2_1",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "Fight and Die",
          "children": []
        },
        {
          "id": "2_2",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "Run",
          "children": []
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "3",
      "question": "",
      "answer": "Master",
      "children": []
    },
    {
      "id": "4",
      "question": "",
      "answer": "Champion",
      "children": []
    },
    {
      "id": "5",
      "question": "",
      "answer": "Elder God",
      "children": []
    }
  ]
}
